acausedesgarcons.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy - Sturb - Gay App

## Privacy

Publié le 25 février 2016

## Sturb Privacy Policy

 **Initial Account Creation**

As a gay social networking application, Sturb collects and shares sensitive information concerning its members including their sexual orientation and location.  See Sturb ‘s Privacy Policy for additional information concerning Sturb privacy practices.

 **Notice of Updated Privacy Policy to Existing Users** **  
****Upon Log-in**

 **STURB PRIVACY POLICY**

By accessing the website at **https://sturb.com**  (“Sturb  **Site** ”), the Sturb mobile application (e.g., Sturb  iOS, Sturb  Android) (“Sturb **App** ”), , which are provided by Sturb , with a mailing address of COMSAS – 17 rue de MAdrid – 75008 PARIS (“Sturb ”), you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data (defined below) in accordance with this privacy policy.

 **Types Of Data We Collect**.

We collect personal data and non-personal data about you.  “ **Personal Data** ” means your name and any data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your address, telephone number, e-mail address, geo-location data, device identifier as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data.

The following provides examples of the types of data that we collect, and how we collect them.  Note that not all of the Sturb Services collect all of the data listed below:

Account Credentials| We may require you to provide an phone number to use certain Sturb Service.  
---|---  
Device Information| We may collect certain software and hardware information about your Device. For example, we may collect an ID that is unique to the device on which you install and/or access the Sturb Service (“ **Device ID** ” and “ **Device,** ” respectively).  
Distance Information| When you use the Sturb [**App**](https://boys.one/), we will collect your location to determine your distance from other users (“ **Distance Information** ”) through the GPS, Wi-Fi, and/or cellular technology in your Device. Your last known location is stored on our servers for the purpose of calculating Distance Information between you and other users.  
Log Files| We may collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. We also use cookies and URL information to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the information for which you searched and which you viewed. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer’s hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your device until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Sturb Service and to improve our marketing efforts, including through the use of targeted advertising. Persistent cookies we place may be removed by following instructions provided by your browser.  If you choose to disable cookies, some areas or features of the Sturb Service may not work properly.  
Messages| When you send a message (which may include photos, location, audio, or video) to other users of the Sturb Service, we may retain the message for archival purposes or as otherwise allowed by law.  
Profile Information| We may collect Personal Data from you. For example, in the Sturb App, we may collect your photo, display name, status, relationship, ethnicity, age or date of birth, geo-location data, email address, password for the Sturb Service, height, weight, social network link, “Looking For,” “Favorites,” “Blocks,” “Tribes” and any other information that you voluntarily add to your profile on the Sturb App or that is generated through your use of the Sturb Service. You may also have the option to provide information concerning health characteristics, such as your HIV status. Remember that if you choose to include information in your profile, and make your profile public, that information will also become public. As a result, you should carefully consider what information to include in your profile.  
 |    
Feedback/  
Support| If you provide us feedback or contact us for support we will collect your name and e-mail address and possibly other Personal Data, as well as any other content that you send to us in order to reply and address any issue. If you contact us for support, we may also collect and retain certain technical diagnostic data, such as your phone model.  
 |    
Surveys| When you participate in a survey, we may collect additional information that you provide through the survey.  If the survey is provided by a third party service provider, the third party’s privacy policy applies to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information. Unless noted otherwise, we use Survey Monkey for surveys.  
Partner Promotion| We may collect information that you provide as part of a Partner Promotion (defined below).  
Third Party Platforms| If you use or connect to the Sturb Site or download the Sturb Service through a third party platform, such as Facebook, you allow us to access and/or collect certain information from your third party platform profile/account.  We may also access information contained in cookies placed on your device by the third party platform.  Note that we may share this information with the third party platform for their use.  
Third Party Tracking| Our advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies or other tracking technology which may collect information about you within the Sturb Service. We do not control use of these tracking technologies.  
  
 **Use And Processing Of Your Personal Data.**

In addition to the uses described above, we use your Personal Data in the following ways:

  *  **Identify You**.  To identify you as a user on the Sturb Service.
  *  **Provide Products and Services**. To provide the products and services you request, including the Sturb Service.
  *  **Improve Services**.  To improve the Sturb Service.
  *  **Communicate with you**.  To respond to your inquiries related to support, employment opportunities, or other requests, and to send Promotional Emails to those users that request or authorize them.
  *  **Partner Promotions**.  To conduct a Partner Promotion that you request.
  *  **Marketing and Advertising**. For marketing and promotional purposes, including to inform you of products, services or offers of Sturb , our related companies or business partners that may be of interest to you.
  *  **Administration**. For internal administrative purposes, as well as to administer or manage our relationship with you, including to communicate with you regarding your use of Sturb Services.
  *  **Employment**. If you apply for employment with Sturb or currently work for Sturb , to manage your employment application, assess your qualifications, and manage your employment with us (applies solely to the Sturb Site).

 **Sharing Of Personal Data.**

In addition to the specific situations discussed above, we disclose Personal Data in the following situations:

  *  **User Profiles** **.  **The Sturb App is a social networking platform that is designed to allow users to share information.  When you use the Sturb App, your Profile Information is public, and other users of the Sturb App can see your Profile Information and other Personal Data (including sensitive personal data) posted by you.  For example, other users can search for you, search for your profile characteristics, or see you listed as being in their vicinity. Do not include information in your profile that you want to keep private.  While the Sturb App may permit you to make certain items (e.g., Profile Information, preferences, opinions of other users, or other information) non-public, sophisticated users who use the Sturb App in an unauthorized manner may nevertheless be able to obtain this information and may be able to determine your identity. By becoming a member, you authorize that your photos are used for marketing purposes by our platform.
  *  **Distance Information.**  The Sturb **App** is designed to allow users to share Distance Information. As a result, Distance Information is public, and other users of the Sturb App can see your Distance Information (including how many feet or meters you are from them). Sturb App users can use the search feature in the Sturb App to search for other users by distance. Your Distance Information will be used for these searches. Sophisticated users who use the Sturb App in an unauthorized manner, or other users who change their location while you remain in the same location, may use this information to determine your exact location and may be able to determine your identity.  Please note: even if you choose to hide your Distance Information, the Sturb App will continue to sort and display your profile based on your relative distance from other users, so your Distance Information may still be approximated by other users. Thus, even if you choose to hide your Distance Information, others may nevertheless be able to determine your location.

  *  **Third Party Tracking Companies**. We may share your hashed Device ID, Profile Information, Distance Information, and demographic information with our advertising and analytics partners. These third parties may also collect information directly from you as described in this Privacy Policy. The privacy policy of these third party companies applies to their collection, use and disclosure of your information. For example, two of our many partners are Google Analytics and Flurry Analytics. Google Analytics and Flurry Analytics collect information anonymously and report website trends without identifying individual visitors.
  *  **Third Party Service Providers**. We may share your Personal Data with third party service providers to: provide you with the Sturb Service; conduct quality assurance testing; provide technical support; and/or to provide other services to Sturb .  Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, these third party service providers are required by contract not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by Sturb .
  *  **Partner Promotion**. We may offer contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions with third party partners.  If you decide to enter a contest, sweepstakes, or promotion that is sponsored by a third party partner the information that you provide will be shared with us and with them.  Their use of your information is not governed by this privacy policy.
  *  **Affiliates and Acquisitions**. We may share your Personal Data with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control.  If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.
  *  **Other Disclosures**. Sturb may disclose Personal Data in response to subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, or in connection with any legal process, or to comply with relevant laws; to establish or exercise our rights to defend against legal claims; if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, violation of our policies, or as otherwise required by law.

 **Your Choices.**

You can make the following choices regarding your Personal Data:

  *  **Promotional Emails**. You may choose during the registration process to provide us with your email address for the purpose of allowing us to send free newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to Sturb and/or the Sturb Service, as well as targeted offers from third parties.  You can stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions in e-mails that you receive.  If you decide not to receive promotional emails, we may still send you service related communications, and our applications may deliver notifications directly to your mobile device.
  *  **Behavioral Advertising**. If you are using the Sturb Service on an Apple iOS device, you may opt out of behavioral targeting by going into Settings > Privacy > Advertising on your iOS device, or visiting Apple’s website for more information.
  *  **Changes To Your Personal Data**. Sturb relies on you to update and correct your Personal Data.  You can modify or delete your profile within the Sturb Service.  Please note that Sturb may keep historical information and content in our backup files and archives as permitted by law and to the extent we anticipate that the information may be required in connection with the original purpose of the collection, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
  *  **Deletion Of Your Personal Data**. Typically we retain your Personal Data for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.  You may, however, request that we delete your Personal Data.  All requests must be directed to the contact in the “Contact Information” section of the Sturb Service.  We may also decide to delete your data at any time if we believe that the data is incomplete, inaccurate, or that our continued use and storage are contrary to our obligations to other individuals or third parties.  When we delete Personal Data, it will be removed from our active database, but it may remain in archives where it is not practical or possible to delete it. In addition, we may keep your Personal Data and usage history (which includes a history of text or photos that have been censored, bans, as well as a history of profile photos uploaded) as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and/or enforce any of our agreements.
  *  **Revocation Of Consent**.  The Sturb Service relies on the processing of Personal Data that you have provided. If you revoke your consent for the processing of Personal Data, then we will no longer be able to provide the Sturb Service. In some cases, we may limit or deny your request if the law permits or requires us to do so, or if we are unable to adequately verify your identity.
  *  **Access To Your Personal Data**. If required by law, upon request, Sturb will grant a user reasonable access to the Personal Data that Sturb holds about the user. All requests must be directed to the contact in the “Contact Information” section of the Sturb Service.

 **How We Protect Personal Information**

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure. While Sturb uses reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, Sturb cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Data. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of any unauthorized access to your Personal Data, we may notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if permitted to do so by law.

 **Miscellaneous Information**

The following additional information relates to our privacy practices:

  *  **Permissible Age**.  The Sturb Service is intended for users 18 years of age and older only (twenty-one (21) years of age in places where eighteen (18) years is not the age of majority). We do not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of majority. If you are aware that a child or minor has submitted Personal Data on the Sturb Service, please contact us using the information provided below so that we can take appropriate action.
  *  **Transmission Of Data To Other Countries**. Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.  Therefore, in some circumstances, you might be left without a legal remedy in the event of a privacy breach. By submitting your Personal Data, you agree to this transfer, storage and/or processing, including all associated risks.
  *  **Third Party Applications/Websites**.  We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for other websites or applications.  If you click on a link to another website or third party application, the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply.
  *  **Contact Information**.  Sturb welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please contact us at the following:

contact@sturb.com

Sturb will also initiate a prompt investigation if you contact us with a complaint against our privacy practices or a concern that our practices do not conform to the requirements in your jurisdiction.  We will attempt, where practical, to ensure ongoing compliance with any legal obligations.

  *  **Changes To This Privacy Policy.  If we make a material change to this policy we will, at a minimum, attempt to notify you of that change by either sending an e-mail to the last e-mail address that you provided to us (if any), or notifying you when you log into the Sturb Service.  Continued use of the Sturb Service indicates your agreement that any information relating to you, regardless of when it was collected, will be governed by Sturb’s  current policy.**

 **Last Revised: February, 2017**
